* BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

    * Back

    * Back

    * Hi

Hi

    * BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

        * BACK

    * Back

    * Back

Privacy Policy
==============

_Last updated: 9/26/2022_

We have created this Privacy Policy to explain how information you provide to us is used and shared. This Privacy Policy relates to the information collection and use practices of Smith Brothers Farms in connection with our services (the "Services"), which are made available to you through a variety of platforms, including our website: https://www.smithbrothersfarms.com and mobile applications (the "Sites").

By visiting our Sites and using our Services, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the accompanying Terms of Service.

**The Information We Collect**

1) Contact Information. When you sign up (create an account or sign in using Facebook or Google authentication), you are required to provide us with information about yourself (collectively, the "Contact Information"). Such Contact  Information may include your name, email address, mailing address, and phone number. We do not collect any Contact Information from you when you use the Services unless you provide us with the Contact Information voluntarily (directly or via Facebook or Google authentication.)

2) Billing Information. When you sign up, you are required to provide payment information in addition to the Contact Information noted above. Such information may include a payment card number, billing name and address, and similar information (collectively, the “Billing Information”).

3) Other Information. In addition to the Contact Information and the Billing Information noted above that you voluntarily provide to us, we may collect additional information (collectively, the “Other Information”). Such Other Information may include:

a. From Your Activity. Information that we automatically collect when you use the Sites and Services, such as your IP addresses, browser type and language, referring and exit pages and URLs, date and time, amount of time spent on particular pages, what sections of the Sites you visit, order information, and similar information concerning your use of the Services.

b. From Cookies. Information that we collect using “cookie” technology. Cookies are small packets of data that our Sites store on your device to “remember” information about your visit. We use cookies to help us collect Other Information and to enhance your experience using the Services. If you do not want the Sites to place a cookie on your device, you may be able to turn "cookies" off on your computer or mobile device. Please refer to your internet browser(s) or device settings for information on how to do this. However, if you decide not to accept cookies from us, the Services may not function properly.

c. From You. Additional information about yourself that you voluntarily provide to us, such as product and service reviews, product preferences and emails sent to us.

d. From Third-Party Web Beacons and Third-Party Buttons. We may display third-party content on the Sites. Third-party content may use cookies, web beacons, or other mechanisms for obtaining data in connection with your viewing of the third-party content on the Sites. Additionally, we may implement third party buttons (such as Facebook “like” or “share” buttons) that may function as web beacons even when you do not interact with the button. Information collected through third-party web beacons and buttons is collected directly by these third parties, not by Smith Brothers Farms. Information collected by a third party in this manner is subject to that third party’s own data collection, use, and disclosure policies.

e. From Other Sources. Information that we collect or receive from other sources, such as our partners.

**Accessing and Modifying Personal Information and Communication Preferences**

If you have registered for the Services, you may access, review, and make changes to your Contact Information and Billing Information by following the instructions found on our Sites. In addition, you may manage your receipt of marketing and non-transactional communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of any Smith Brothers Farms marketing email. Active customers cannot opt out of receiving transactional emails related to their account. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to process such requests in a timely manner. You should be aware, however, that it is not always possible to completely remove or modify information in our subscription databases.

**How We Use and Share the Information**

We use the Contact Information, the Billing Information, and the Other Information to process transactions; provide you the Services; solicit your feedback; inform you about our products, services, upcoming events, recipes, and special promotions; administer and process contests, promotions, and sweepstakes; conduct analytics; and improve our Services to you. Also, we may share Contact Information, the Billing Information, and/or Other Information as described below.

* In order to administer our contests, promotions, and sweepstakes, we may share your Contact Information and Other Information with our third-party promotional and marketing partners.
* In an ongoing effort to better understand our users and our Services, we might analyze the Other Information in aggregate form in order to operate, maintain, manage, and improve the Services. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. We may share this aggregate data with our affiliates, agents, and business partners. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our products and Services to current and prospective business partners and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.
* We may share Other Information about your activity on the Sites with third parties for the purpose of analytics or tailoring, analyzing, managing, reporting, and optimizing advertising you see (on our Sites or elsewhere). These third parties may use cookies, pixel tags (also called web beacons or clear gifs), and/or other technologies to collect such Other Information for such purposes. Pixel tags enable us, and these third-party advertisers, to recognize a browser’s cookie when a browser visits the site on which the pixel tag is located, in order to learn which advertisement brings a user to a given site.
* As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution, or similar event, the Contact Information, the Billing Information, and the Other Information may be part of the transferred assets.
* To the extent permitted by law, we may also disclose Contact Information, the Billing Information, and the Other Information when required by law, court order, or other government or law enforcement authority or regulatory agency, or whenever we believe that disclosing the such information is necessary or advisable, for example, to protect the rights, property, or safety of Smith Brothers Farms or others.

**How We Protect Your Information**

We take commercially reasonable steps to protect the Contact Information, the Billing Information, and the Other Information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Please understand, however, that no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to and from us over the Internet. In particular, email sent to or from us may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email.

**Requesting Review and Deletion of Personal Information**

You may request to review and delete the Personal Information that we have collected from you. To request to review and delete your Personal Information, please send email to privacy@smithbrothersfarms.com. Please include your account email address and summarize your request in the email. We may reply back to you to confirm receipt or collect additional details in order to complete your request. Please note, your right to review and delete Personal Information is subject to exceptions. For example, we may need to retain your Personal Information to provide you with the Services, complete a transaction or comply with other actions you have requested.

**Important Notice to Non-U.S. Residents**

The Sites and the Services are operated in the United States and is intended for visitors located within the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using the Services and/or providing us with any information, you consent to this transfer.

If you choose to use the Service from the European Union or other regions of the world with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, then please note that you are transferring your personal information outside of those regions to the United States for storage and processing. Also, we may transfer your data from the U.S. to other countries or regions in connection with storage and processing of data, fulfilling your requests, and operating the Service. By providing any information, including personal information, on or to the Service, you consent to such transfer, storage, and processing.

**Children**

Our Sites and Services are not intended for children. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13 through the Sites and Services. If you are under 13, please do not give us any Personal Information. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children to never provide Personal Information through the Services without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information to us, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

**External Websites**

The Sites may contain links to third-party websites. Smith Brothers Farms has no control over the privacy practices or the content of any of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors, or other websites to which we provide links. As such, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of those third-party websites. You should check the applicable third-party privacy policy and terms of use when visiting any other websites.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date stated at the top of this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and will post any changes on the Sites as soon as they go into effect. By accessing the Sites or using the Services after we make any such changes to this Privacy Policy, you are deemed to have accepted such changes. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.

**How to Contact Us**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please email us at privacy@smithbrothersfarms.com.

###### Get To Know Us

* [Recipes & More (blog)](https://www.smithbrothersfarms.com/blog "Recipes & More (blog)")

###### Let Us Help You

###### Get In Touch

* [26401 79th Ave S  
    Kent, WA 98032](https://goo.gl/maps/1pGKzqBz1bcAkwUY8 "Smith Brothers Farms Address")

###### Download Our App

Copyright © 2024 Smith Brothers Farms. All rights reserved.

* * *

* * *

YES NO

×
